AI can remember previous conversations, but it cannot guarantee which information is current confirmed truth. LOGOS Continuity protects canonical state in real long-running projects.
With Codex, I built a working public product. Judge Mode is only an optional guide through the real state engine, approval rules, and GPT integration.
Command Center identifies the most urgent continuity risks and routes the user to the correct resolution workflow.
This sample is a real release workflow. GPT-5.6 identifies the intended project, while LOGOS restores approved plans, current validation state, next actions, and warnings as separate layers.
GPT-5.6 structures the user's intent, but it cannot directly change canonical truth. This statement remains in Exploration until the user explicitly approves a change.
Conflicting claims never silently overwrite canonical state. The user can keep the existing decision, apply a temporary exception, or approve a new canonical decision.
Current State, Next Actions, Exploration, and recovery checkpoints remain separate and manageable in one operational view.
Whenever canonical state changes, LOGOS records what changed, why it changed, and where the information came from.
The next session does not have to guess from the full conversation again. It starts from verified project state, unresolved risks, and the correct next action in authority order.
LOGOS turns long-running AI work from probabilistic recall into approval-gated, provenance-aware continuity.